{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "name": "inverse-functions",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\ln{(x+2)}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(2)$$.",
          "solution": "e^{2}-2",
          "answer": 5.389056,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\ln{(x-2)}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(2)$$.",
          "solution": "e^{2}+2",
          "answer": 9.389056,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        }
      ],
      "numQuestions": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "hyperbolic-functions",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sinh{(x+2)}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(2)$$.",
          "solution": "e^{2}-2",
          "answer": 5.389056,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\ln{(x-2)}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(2)$$.",
          "solution": "e^{2}+2",
          "answer": 9.389056,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        },
        {
          "question": "f(x)=\\sin{(x)}, \\footnotesize{-\\frac{\\pi}{2} \\leq x \\leq \\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
          "questionPrompt": "Calculate $$f^{-1}(\\frac{\\pi}{6})$$.",
          "solution": "\\arcsin{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
          "answer": 0.55107,
          "status": "unattempted"
        }
      ],
      "numQuestions": 10
    }
  ]
}
